#### **Adam Sixsmith**

## adamsixsmith@sky.com - 07867411199

## 66 North End Drive, Harlington, Doncaster, DN5 7JS

## **Personal Profile**

I am a polite, reliable and well-organised individual with 14 years of contact center experience. I excel both independently and as part of a team. I am also studying for an undergraduate degree in Computing and IT with the Open University.

## **Work Experience**

# Outbound Sales Advisor – October 2013 – August 2015

Concentrix, Adwick Park, Manvers, Rotherham, South Yorkshire, S63 5NA

### Responsibilities:

- Calling customers to pitch products and services
- Processing orders when a customer has agreed to a sale
- Calling customers back when promised

# Inbound Webchat Retentions Advisor – August 2015 - August 2019

Concentrix, Adwick Park, Manvers, Rotherham, South Yorkshire, S63 5NA

# Responsibilities:

- Taking inbound chats from customers wishing to leave the company
- Negotiating deals with customers wishing to leave the company or looking for a better deal.
- Generating upgrade and disconnection orders, depending on what has been discussed with the customer

#### Deputy Team Leader - August 2019 - February 2022

Concentrix, Adwick Park, Manvers, Rotherham, South Yorkshire, S63 5NA

## Responsibilities:

- Providing coaching to team members and giving them guidance and direction.
- Getting an understanding of the strengths and weaknesses of my team members and using this when organising tasks and setting goals.
- Resolving conflict with both team members and customers.
- Hosting team meetings to celebrate team members successes and use this time to give updates or have little team bonding sessions.

# **Team Leader - February 2022 - Present**

Concentrix, Adwick Park, Manvers, Rotherham, South Yorkshire, S63 5NA

## Responsibilities:

- Chairing disciplinary meetings with members of the team for conduct or capability issues.
- Providing coaching to team members and giving them guidance and direction.
- Getting an understanding of the strengths and weaknesses of my team members and using this when organising tasks and setting goals.
- Resolving conflict with both team members and customers.
- Hosting team meetings to celebrate team members successes and use this time to give updates or have little team bonding sessions

## **EDUCATION**

**BSc (Honours) Computing and IT (Software)** 

The Open University

April 2023 – August 2030 (In Progress)

**B-Tech National Diploma in Sport Level 3** 

**Dearne Valley College, Manvers** 

September 2009 – 2011

• Grade: PASS, PASS

#### **GCSEs**

#### 2009

Leisure and Tourism: B, CResistant Materials: CReligious Education: C

Physical Education: C

Science: C, DMaths: D

• English Language: D

• English Literature: E

# References

Available on request